紙牌屋
前情提要
我們是美國公民
"We are citizens of the United States.
我們被作為人質扣押
We have been taken hostage.
我們不會和罪犯弗蘭克·安德伍德溝通
We will not communicate with the criminal Frank Underwood.
我們只和他的繼任者威廉·康威溝通
We will only communicate with his successor, William Conway.
要么滿足我們的要求  否則他們就得死
Either you give us what we want or we kill them.
他偷了你的總統之位你就不生氣嗎
Aren't you angry that he stole your presidency?
沃克公開聲明了
Walker went on record.
只要我們站出來  他就完了
You and I go on the record, he's done.
轉錄  馬上做
Transcribe this, right away.
他要在文章里寫我們曾威脅曝光他們
He's putting in the article that we threatened to expose them.
怎么會發生這種事
How did this happen?
你就要成為下一位美國第一夫人了
You're gonna be the next First Lady of the United States.
我們讓這件事為我們所用
We make it work for us.
恐懼
Fear.
我受夠了試圖贏取人心
I'm done trying to win over people's hearts.
安德伍德或許是個壞蛋  但他不會殺人
Underwood may be a crook, but he's not a killer.
那是假定他會死
It presumes he's going to die.
他就是會死
He is going to die.
我們不向恐怖低頭
We don't submit to terror.
我們制造恐怖
We make the terror.
我一直想跟你談談
I've been meaning to talk with you.
真可怕  不是嗎
It's terrifying, isn't it?
總統和我有一個簡單的請求
The president and I have a simple request.
告訴我們你看到了什么
Tell us what you see.
如果你周圍有任何東西
If anything in your environment
讓你覺得奇怪  不對勁
strikes you as a bit odd, a bit off,
拿起電話
pick up the phone.
不管是個包裹  還是不太對勁的人
Whether it's a package or a person that seems out of place,
我們希望你通知我們
we'd love you to let us know.
因為如今外面有很多雜音
Because there's a lot of noise out there these days.
媒體嘰嘰喳喳  沉湎于過去
A noisy press that's choosing to dwell on the past
卻不關注當下的事
instead of what's happening right now.
我丈夫和我想保護你
My husband and I want to protect you.
兩周后  你們將前往投票箱
In two weeks' time, you will be heading to the ballot box
決定你們要生活在怎樣的國家里
to decide what kind of country you want to live in.
這個選擇影響深遠
It's a profound choice.
但不管誰贏得選舉
But no matter who wins this election,
我們得通力合作
we're going to need to work together,
互相照應
watch out for each other,
是的  也互相監督
and, yes, watch each other,
以確保所有人的安全
to keep us all safe and sound.
告訴我們你看到了什么
Tell us what you see.
我叫克萊爾·安德伍德  我認可這則信息
My name is Claire Underwood, and I approve this message.
我們要再拍一條嗎
Should we do one more?
民主黨來了嗎
Did the Democrats show?
他們沒讓人失望  幾乎都來了  先生
They didn't disappoint. Almost every member, sir.
-幾乎  -我列了到場名單
- Almost. - I have a list of those who did.
各位國會議員  我不需要《華盛頓先驅報》
My fellow congressmen, I do not need the Washington Herald
告訴我白宮里住了個惡棍
to tell me that a scoundrel lives in the White House.
我看到民主黨來了
I can see the Democrats are here.
他們急著辯論
They're eager to debate.
我對過道另一邊的先生們說
I say to the gentlemen on the other side of the aisle...
謝謝
thank you.
我們是否該調查總統
Should we investigate the president
在就任副總統期間犯下的罪行
for crimes committed while he was vice president?
我說  好  我們辯論吧
I say, yes. Let's debate.
我們整日整夜地辯論這惡棍
Let's debate this miscreant all day and all night.
議長女士  議事詢問
Madam Speaker. Parliamentary inquiry.
佐治亞州的議員
The gentleman from Georgia
請提出他的議事詢問
may state the nature of his parliamentary inquiry.
難道按眾議院規則
Do the rules of the House not require
總統不是該受到正式邀請才能出席嗎
the president be formally invited in order to attend?
議長女士  容我說一句
Madam Speaker, if I may...
議長有請南卡羅萊納州議員說話
The Speaker recognizes the gentleman from South Carolina.
總統今天戴了他的國會胸針
The president is wearing his congressional pin today
所以他可以出席一切會議
and is thereby welcome to any and all proceedings.
議長女士  議長女士
Madam Speaker! Madam Speaker!
按眾議院規則
Rules of the House state
前眾議院成員若與議題
that former members are not allowed on the floor
有直接關系則不得參與辯論
when they have interest in the matter under debate.
議長女士
Madam Speaker,
總統對今天的議題
the president has no interest
既無關聯  也無意見
or opinion on the matter being debated today.
眾議院安靜  眾議院安靜
The House suspend. The House will suspend.
議長女士  我還在講話
Madam Speaker, I still do have the floor,
而且我難以相信
and I find it hard to believe
總統對議題無話可說
the president wouldn't have an opinion on the matter being discussed.
如果佛羅里達州議員
If the good gentleman from Florida
肯讓出點時間
would yield a portion of his time,
他的疑問肯定能得到解答
I assure him it will satisfy his query.
我給黨領袖三分鐘時間
I yield three minutes to the leader.
我把我的時間讓給前南卡羅萊納州議員
And I yield my time to the former congressman from South Carolina
現美國總統
and the President of the United States.
議事程序  議事詢問
Point of order! Parliamentary inquiry!
議事詢問
Parliamentary inquiry!
總統先生  這太不尋常了
Mr. President. This is beyond the norm.
我不在乎
I don't care.
而且我也不在乎
And I also do not care
你們的調查委員會
about your investigative committees.
不  那不是我今天關心的東西
No, that is not what I care about today.
眾議院安靜
The House will cease.
那不是我今天關心的東西
That is not what I care about today.
我要去出席
I am on my way
一個美國愛國者的葬禮
to the funeral of an American patriot.
一個好人  一個丈夫
A good man, a husband...
一個父親
a father...
在美國境內被人砍頭
who was beheaded on American soil.
眾議院
And this chamber
卻在今天辯論我
chooses to debate me?
-眾議院安靜  -我要求
- The House will suspend. - I asked to speak
向眾議院發表講話  卻遭到拒絕
to a full session of this chamber and my requests were denied.
-議長女士  -總統先生  你必須讓出說話權
- Madam Speaker! - Mr. President, you must yield the floor.
我不會退讓的  議長女士
I will not yield, Madam Speaker.
因為我等不了
Because I cannot wait.
其中一個殺人犯
One of the murderers...
殺害了吉姆·米勒先生的一個殺人犯
One of the murderers who killed Mr. Jim Miller...
還逍遙法外
is still out there.
正在逃逸
At large.
你們還要多少證據
How much more proof do you people need?
我要求所有眾議院議員表明立場
I demand that every member of this House take a stand.
就像曾經的羅斯福  再之前的威爾遜
Like FDR before, and Wilson before him.
我要求國會
I demand that this Congress
正式對哈里發國宣戰
declare a formal declaration of war against ICO,
在本土  也在海外
both here and abroad.
動議休會
Motion to adjourn.
-支持  -眾議院休會
- Second! - The House will adjourn.
-總統請停止講話  -我不會停止
- The president will cease. - I will not cease!
我絕不停止
I will never cease.
我要求國會宣布美利堅合眾國
I demand that this Congress declare a state of war
已經并且正在
has existed and does exist
與哈里發國交戰
between ICO and the United States of America.
我要求所有眾議院成員留在這里
And I demand that every member of this House stay in this chamber
不管要多久
for as long as it takes,
直到你們對我的要求作出表決
until you bring my request to a vote.
否則你們將被歷史
Or you will all go down in history
銘記為懦夫
as cowards!
懦夫
Cowards!
請警衛官帶走總統
The sergeant at arms will remove the president.
議長女士  我重復  我要求投票
Madam Speaker, I repeat. I demand a vote.
我不會退讓
I will not yield.
翻譯   草草
時間軸   萌
時間軸   Kallen
后期   餓得慌
顧問   老杜
校對   草草
總監   草草
紙牌屋
人人影視傾情奉獻
第五季  第一集
對馬斯特森的搜尋仍在繼續
國內恐怖分子在逃
據稱的恐怖分子扎克瑞·霍松被聯調局擊斃
Alleged terrorist Zachary Hawthorne was killed by the FBI,
但約書亞·馬斯特森仍在逃
but Joshua Masterson is still at large.
米勒一家哀悼之時
While the Miller family mourns,
對逃跑的恐怖分子的搜尋仍在繼續
the hunt for the missing terrorist continues
氣氛十分緊張
and tensions are running high.
總統雖然提出戰爭
The president may be asking for war,
但看來他已經遭遇了戰爭
but it seems war's already been declared on him.
總統肖像被焚燒
中東對總統做出反應
爆發反安德伍德抗議
我的粉絲
My fans.
聯調局正在調查查塔努加市的一起連環槍擊案
FBI is looking into a multiple shooting in Chattanooga.
-據報稱是與黑幫有關  -不行
- Reports have it gang related. - No.
西弗吉尼亞州一架私人飛機墜毀  機械故障
A private plane went down in West Virginia. Mechanical failure.
佐治亞州多處房屋失火
A series of homes were set on fire in Georgia,
很可能是縱火
most likely arson.
北卡羅來納州一家便利店
Convenience store in North Carolina
今晨4點左右爆炸
exploded at about 4:00 in the morning.
-商店在哪  -羅利郊外
- Where's the store? - Uh, suburb outside of Raleigh.
起因仍在調查
The cause is still under investigation.
-我去露個臉  -是  夫人
- I'll make an appearance. - Yes, ma'am.
加在日程里  讓媒體有時間出動
Just put it on the schedule so the media has time to mobilize.
是  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
總統對約書亞·馬斯特森宣戰了吧
I take it the president has declared war on Joshua Masterson.
他就不該不讓我繼續參加通話
He never should've kicked me off that call.
但今天早晨的重點不是政治
But this morning isn't about politics.
是啊
That's right.
我們得對生者表示同情
We need to show some compassion for the living.
對死者表示尊重
And respect for the dead.
他們一家答應了短暫見面
The family's agreed to a moment.
沒有媒體  不做講話  但我們應該能做點什么
No press, no speeches, but we should be able to pull something.
-總統先生  -州長
- Mr. President. - Governor.
他們不知道我們已經為他們做了什么嗎
Do they not realize what we've done for them already?
這我說了  先生  但是
I pointed that out, sir, but...
他們家的女兒服了藥  目前很脆弱
the daughter's medicated and very fragile at the moment.
好吧
All right.
米勒太太
Mrs. Miller.
-我非常遺憾  -謝謝
- I'm so very sorry. - Thank you.
我保證
And I promise you,
我絕不會罷休
I will not stop
除非所有導致了這場慘劇的人
until everyone responsible for this terrible tragedy
都受到裁決
is brought to justice.
我發誓  上帝為證
And I swear to you, as God is my witness...
再不會有人傷害你和你的家人了
no one will ever harm you or your family ever again.
舉國與你和你女兒同哀  米勒太太
The nation mourns with you and your daughter, Mrs. Miller.
-謝謝  如果你不介意  -當然
- Thank you. If you don't mind... - Of course.
總統先生
Mr. President.
我就來
I'll be right along.
你今天很忙  先生
It's a busy day for you today, sir.
今天很悲傷
It's a sad, sad day.
很遺憾結果是這樣
It's a shame things didn't turn out differently.
是啊  有些事比我們倆重要  威爾
Yes. Well, some things are bigger than the two of us, Will.
我不希望他在場
I don't want him here!
冷靜  梅莉莎  求你
Calm down, Melissa. Please.
都怪他  他死了
It's his fault. He's dead.
-爸爸死了  他殺了他  -求你
- Daddy's dead. He killed him. - Please.
給我點時間
Give me a minute.
-你吃藥了嗎  -吃了  好嗎
- Did you take your medicine? - Yes. Okay?
吃了  吃了
Yes. Yes!
在今天這樣的日子  你會去想  該說什么
You do. You think about what you would say on a day like today.
如果今天這樣的日子出現
If a day like today were to happen.
但你會讓它過去
But you let it pass...
因為你知道  你未來還有漫長的人生
because you know you have so much more left ahead of you.
有很多事可以一起做
So much to do together.
你會想  你想40分鐘
You think... You think 40 minutes...
如果我們遲了40分鐘
If we were late 40 minutes...
或是兩分鐘  哪怕一分鐘
Or two, or one...
或是我們當時去了別處吃飯
Or if we went somewhere else to eat...
但沉湎過去  活在假設里
But to dwell in the past, to live in what-ifs...
那不是我丈夫的為人
That wasn't my husband.
那不是我們
That wasn't us...
-親愛的  -求你
- Honey... - Please.
好  來吧
Okay. Come on.
我得
I need to...
我想說說我父親
I wanted to say about my father...
他是那么堅強  那么勇敢
He was so strong... so brave.
我父親本打算帶我們去
My father was taking us to...
我父親
My father...
-沒事  寶貝  沒事的  -我父親
- Come on, baby. It's okay. - My father...
你殺了我父親  他是因為你才死的
You killed my father. You're the reason he died.
梅莉莎
Melissa...
沒事的  梅莉莎  我們理解
It's all right, Melissa. We understand.
我希望你死  而她當上總統
I hope you die and she becomes president.
那女孩對你說了什么
What did the girl say to you?
她說她希望我死  而你當上總統
She said she hopes I die and that you become the president.
麥卡倫先生  我是國安局副局長邁克爾斯
Mr. Macallan, this is Deputy Director Michaels from the NSA.
我就在你辦公室  我們安排了會面
I'm literally in your office. I believe we had a meeting.
從北到南已經展開了大范圍搜索
There's been raids as far up as New York and down to the panhandle.
到目前為止
As of now,
格林主要在搜索
Green's focusing in on the
弗吉尼亞和北卡羅來納的交界處
border between Virginia and North Carolina.
賽斯為今天下午的事準備好了聲明
Seth has a statement ready for this afternoon.
不  最好的聲明就是不做聲明
No. The best statement is no statement.
再說  我們準備好前
Besides, I want Claire to be the voice on this
我要克萊爾來就此事發聲
until we're ready.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
-外面人好多  -我們最好先讓博奇進來
- Quite a crowd out there. - Well, we better bring Birch in first.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
博奇議員
Congressman Birch.
鮑勃
Bob.
今早的事能載入史冊了  是吧
Well, that was a little bit of history this morning, wasn't it?
-可不是呢  -我看不出有別的辦法
- It certainly was. - I couldn't see it any other way.
我也同意
No disagreement from here.
你了解共和黨的
Well, you know how the Republicans are.
優柔寡斷
Anything but a decision.
他們錯把抱怨當做了領導
They mistake complaint for leadership.
現在沒有調查你的委員會了
Well, instead of a committee to investigate you,
而是成立了討論宣戰的委員會
you got one to discuss your declaration.
直到選舉日
All the way to election day.
哪怕有那么一小撮
Even if there's only a handful
有勇氣和決心敢抵抗的共和黨人
of Republicans with the grit and spit to put up a fight,
我們都能控制輿論
we can control the conversation.
讓他們談什么都好  就是別談那篇文章
Get them talking about anything but that goddamn article.
好了  我們這邊
All right. Now, who from our side
-得去安撫誰  -烏麥克
- do we need to massage? - Womack.
那聲明讓他措手不及  得讓他別摻和
The declaration caught him off guard. Had to keep him out of it.
是他的選民真要去打仗
It's his constituents that actually fight the damn thing.
請尊敬的密蘇里州議員進來吧
Well, let's call in the honorable gentleman from Missouri.
-他喜歡波本吧  -是的
- Oh, he's a bourbon man, isn't he? - Yes, he is.
噱頭  是的  我說這是噱頭
A stunt. Yes, I'm calling it a stunt.
查理  容我說
Charlie, if I may...
湯姆  請說說  你什么意思
Tom, please, what are you implying?
這宣戰請求不過又是在分散注意力
This request for a declaration of war is yet another distraction.
我從未像今天這樣為總統自豪
And I've never been prouder of the president than I am today.
我不是在否認米勒一家的遭遇  那是個慘劇
I'm not denying what happened to the Millers. It was a tragedy.
不  你在否認  否認它就是慘劇
No, but you are. Because denying it is the tragedy.
這是個規律
This is a pattern.
你丈夫的政府  安德伍德夫人
Your husband's administration, Mrs. Underwood,
-繼續在暗箱操作  -湯姆
- continues to operate in the shadows. - Tom...
我知道你相信你的文章很重要
I understand you believe in the importance of your article.
我答應今天來跟你談談它
And I agreed to come here today and talk with you about it.
但我們正在奮力保護國家的安全
But we're fighting to keep this country safe.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood,
白宮尚未發表任何關于
the White House has yet to release one piece of information
抓捕那些國內恐怖分子的情況
about the attempted capture of those domestic terrorists.
哈里發國恐怖分子  是的
ICO terrorists, yes.
據幾小時前的報告稱
Reports from a few hours ago
是在北卡羅來納或弗吉尼亞州
are saying North Carolina or Virginia.
但目前也只有這些
But that's all we have.
我們在慢慢收緊包圍圈
Well, we are circling in, we're getting closer.
我告訴你
I will tell you,
我們的情報部門  是真正的英雄
our intelligence community, they are the real heroes.
查理  請回到我的點上  我的消息源確認
Charlie, if we could get back to my point, my sources confirmed--
湯姆
Tom.
海瑟·鄧巴  她不是我或我丈夫的朋友
Heather Dunbar, no friend of mine or my husband's,
調查過這些指控  但宣布總統無罪
looked into these charges, and cleared the president.
無罪  得了吧
Cleared? Please.
白宮自《先驅報》刊登了我的文章
The White House has not had a single press briefing
就沒舉行過一次新聞發布會
since the Herald ran my article.
你總說白宮不就此事發言
You keep saying the White House isn't speaking about this.
但我正坐在這里跟你說話
I am sitting right here talking to you.
不是雷米·丹頓或杰姬·夏普
Not Remy Danton or Jackie Sharp.
也不是盧卡斯·古德溫
Or Lucas Goodwin, either.
-什么  -什么意思  盧卡斯·古德溫
- What? - Excuse me. Lucas Goodwin, meaning?
我是說  我  我在這兒
I'm saying, me. I'm here.
我不知道這些話我們還要說多少遍
And I don't know how many more times we have to go over this.
湯姆·漢默施密特的文章以前
You know, a Tom Hammerschmidt article used to be
是我打開《華盛頓先驅報》后
the first thing I would look for
第一個要找的東西
when I opened the Washington Herald.
安德伍德夫婦停止了競選宣傳
The Underwoods are no longer campaigning.
他們想怎么說怎么說
They can call it what they want.
如果你想想過去的幾天  想想現在的氣氛
Well, if you think about the last few days, what's in the air...
或許我們慢慢來
It might not be such a bad idea for us to
也不是壞事
take it one handshake at a time.
或者實話實說
Or call it for what it is.
"國內和國外"
"Home and abroad."
總統基本上在要求許可
The president is essentially asking for permission
在我們的國土上打仗
to fight a war on our soil.
我們不能太強烈反對
We can't push back too hard.
我們不能顯得好像對恐怖主義手軟
We can't afford to look soft on terror.
我們也不能視而不見
We can't look the other way, either.
你最清楚這樣的話會帶來的結果
You of all people know where this kind of talk leads.
哈里發國和美利堅合眾國
...ICO and the United States of America.
確保處理宣戰的委員會
Make sure the committee dealing with the declaration of war
不會進入表決
never gets to a vote.
我們不反對戰爭  我們反對他的戰爭
We're not against war, we're against his.
我要你聯絡議長
And I want you to reach out to the Speaker
查明她要安排誰進入那個委員會
and find out who she's putting on that committee.
我們得回到總統罪行的問題上
We need to get back to the president's crimes.
那才是新聞  唯一的新聞
That's the story. It's the only story.
還有別的嗎
Anything else?
我有我的稿子
I have my script.
我不會退讓
I will not yield!
我不會
I will not...
哈里
Harry...
我想知道他說了什么  什么時候說的
I want to know what he says and when he says it.
將軍可不習慣接受命令
Our general isn't used to taking orders.
威爾  還有
Will, one more thing.
-怎么了  -你妻子
- What? - Your wife.
我知道我們在波利跳上展開了宣傳
Okay, I know we opened up this campaign on Pollyhop,
但或許該中止了
but it might be time to close it down...
或至少也該小心點
or at least be more careful.
他們查到了什么
Well, what did they find out?
他們在找的那名
The home of the mother of the terrorist,
恐怖分子的母親家
you know, the one they're looking for,
昨晚遭人破壞
was vandalized last night.
車庫被燒  窗戶被打破
Garage set on fire. Broken windows.
漢娜
And, uh, Hannah...
她發了視頻
well... she posted.
她在網上維護了那位母親
She was defending the mother online.
-什么時候  -今天下午
- When? - This afternoon.
這個時機可不妙
The timing is not good on this.
-我給你看  -等會兒的
- I can show you. - Not now.
謝謝
Thank you.
康威州長和我很榮幸能來
Governor Conway and I are honored to be here
陪伴米勒一家和他們的親友
with the Miller family and their closest friends.
海外退伍軍人協會
我知道海外退伍軍人協會
I know the VFW
是吉姆在諾克斯維爾生活的重要部分
was a big part of Jim's life here in Knoxville.
在國土安全部和我們熱線的幫助下
With the help of Homeland and our hotline,
我們認為馬斯特森
we think that Masterson
已經進入了弗吉尼亞州的西南角
has crossed into the southwest corner of Virginia.
在斯考特或華盛頓
Scott or Washington.
-然后呢  -然后
- And? - And...
格林助理局長
Assistant Director Green?
我們在依靠空中支援
We're relying on aerial support,
目擊和當地執法部門
sightings and local law enforcement.
但我們比較確信
But we're fairly confident
我們可以在接下來24小時內找到他
we can have him pinned down in the next 24 hours.
總統要我們完全確定
The president wants us to be absolutely sure.
我們不能允許他再跑掉了  這事關飯碗
We can't have him getting away again. Careers are at stake.
這桌上的每個人
Everyone around this table
都清楚情況的嚴重性
is fully aware of the gravity of the situation.
很好  總統知道了會很高興的
Good. The president will be happy to hear that.
好了  你想要什么樣的吻
Okay. What kind of kiss do you want?
-愛斯基摩  -快進
- Eskimo. - In...
快出
and out.
我就回來
I'll be right back.
-你生氣了  -是的
- You're angry. - I am.
我被提了問  我回答了
I was asked a question and I answered.
說得太輕了
That's the least of it.
好吧  我現在不想談這個
Okay, well, I don't want to talk about it right now.
你是想輸掉競選嗎  是嗎
Are you trying to lose this election? Are you?
威爾  得了
Will, stop it.
你維護的這女人
This woman that you're defending...
她兒子砍了別人的頭
Her son just cut someone's head off.
他還逍遙在外
And he's still out there somewhere.
-你知道這看上去什么樣嗎  -別說了
- Do you understand what this looks like? - Stop it.
你知道我們兒子為什么睡不著嗎
Do you want to know why our son can't sleep?
他才八歲  卻失眠了
He's eight years old, and he can't sleep.
因為他做惡夢
Because he's having nightmares.
因為他覺得
Because he thinks
酒店里有頭黑色大狗在到處跑
there's a big black dog running around the hotel.
-狗  -對
- Dog? - Yes.
他閉上眼睛  就能聽到它咆哮
He closes his eyes, and he can hear it growling.
他害怕  威爾
He's scared, Will.
我說那些話是因為那女人也是受害者
I said what I said because that woman is a victim.
我們都是
We all are.
這必須停止了
And it has to stop.
我希望你贏
I want you to win.
去給自己倒一杯酒  我就回來
Get yourself a drink. I'll be right back.
那是他母親  這是漢娜的回應
That's the mother. And this is Hannah's response.
她不是罪犯
She's not a criminal
不該因為她兒子的罪受懲罰
and should not be punished for the sins of her son.
我知道我們都反對
We all, I know, reject
這兩位困惑受傷的青年的說法和行為
the rhetoric and actions of these damaged, troubled young men.
我是說  這是該反省的時候
What I mean is, this is a time for reflection,
而不是進攻
not aggression...
她沒有表示寬恕  但表示了同情
So she's not condoning it, but it is sympathetic.
把約書亞和扎克瑞說成
Plays into the idea that Joshua and Zachary
一對兒尋找目標的困惑青年
were just a pair of troubled kids looking for a cause,
跟普通學校槍擊手沒什么區別
no different than some school shooter.
視頻轉發超過10萬次了
The post has been shared over 100,000 times.
我想跟她談談
I want to talk with her.
-漢娜  -那個母親
- Hannah? - The mother.
我們一直對你在哪露面十分小心
We've been very careful about where you appear.
-莉安  能讓我們單獨待會兒嗎  -當然
- LeAnn, will you excuse us for a moment? - Of course.
我們得加大恐懼感
We need to dial up the terror.
那個母親能幫我們做到
And the mother can help us with that.
但那樣我們還得找到馬斯特森
But that also means we have to locate Masterson.
盡快
Soon.
湯姆在等我
Tom is waiting for me.
你去吧
Well, you go on.
弗蘭西斯
Francis...
我不該在葬禮上哭
I shouldn't have cried at the funeral.
-不  那效果很好  -對我不好
- No, it played beautifully. - Not for me.
跟我來
Come with me.
來吧  告訴他你要遲點到
Come on. Just tell him you'll be late.
-總統先生  -沒事  警官
- Mr. President. - It's all right, Officer.
夫人
Ma'am.
能給我你的目鏡嗎
May I have your scope?
你槍上的目鏡  我保證還回來
Scope on your gun. I promise I'll give it back.
謝謝  過來
Thank you. Come here.
如果你把目鏡舉在離臉稍遠處
Now, if you just hold the scope a little a ways from your face...
往下看  直向下  草坪對面
and look down, straight down, across the lawn...
門那里
right to the gate.
看到他們了嗎
You see them?
那些人想要發聲  有些是支持的  有些反對
Those people want a voice. Some for, some against.
他們也在草坪那頭往這邊看
And they're looking back across the lawn,
看這棟房子  這些窗戶
toward this house and these windows...
他們在想
and they're thinking,
"不知道總統
"I wonder what the president
和第一夫人今晚在做什么
and the First Lady are doing tonight.
他們能保護我們嗎"
And will they be able to protect us?"
我該在場的
I should have been there.
哪里
Where?
你受槍傷時  我真該在場的
When you got shot. I wish I was there.
或許我還能
Maybe I could've...
保護你
protected you.
你瞧  那些人只想
You see, all those people want...
有人保護他們  不用面對可怕的真相
is someone to keep them from what they're afraid to know.
總統和第一夫人今晚要做什么呢  弗蘭西斯
And what are the president and First Lady doing tonight, Francis?
托馬斯不是還等著你呢嗎
Well, I believe Thomas is waiting for you.
謝謝  先生
Thank you, sir.
我們明早見
I'll see you in the morning.
你有煙嗎
Do you have a smoke?
謝謝
Thank you.
*我知道我的人民今晚在想什么*
*I know what my people are thinking tonight*
BGM: I Wonder What the King Is Doing Tonight
*穿過陰影  他們漫步回家*
*As home through the shadows they wander*
*大家都竊笑著*
*Everyone smiling in secret delight*
*他們看著城堡  思索著*
*As they stare at the castle and ponder*
*當風往這邊吹*
*And whenever the wind blows this way*
*你幾乎能聽到大家說*
*You can almost hear everyone say*
*不知國王今晚在做什么*
*I wonder what the king is doing tonight*
我一直在找你
I've been looking for you.
我餓了
I got hungry.
所以去了主廚房
So I went down to the main kitchen.
下面的人真不錯
That's a lovely group of people you have down there.
如果你需要什么  可以叫人拿上來
If there's anything you need, it can be brought up.
我直到吃在嘴里才知道自己需要什么
I didn't know what I needed until I was eating it.
我聽到了總統的聲明
I heard the president's declaration.
很有力
Very compelling.
你究竟怎么想的
What did you really think?
簡直像真的一樣
It was almost like the real thing.
國安局的人很厲害  非常厲害
The NSA has good people. Very good.
-太厲害了  -不如你厲害
- Too good. - Not as good as you.
足以找到我的算法了
Good enough to find my algorithms.
那不代表他們知道我們用它做了什么
That doesn't mean they knew what we were using them for.
不不
No, no.
前一秒  他們還叫我回家  然后緊接著
One second, they send me home, and then the next,
他們說  "回來"
they tell me, "Come back!"
他們肯定要監視我了  這是個陷阱
They'll been watching me. This is a trap.
或是唯一的出路
Or the only way out.
該死
God damn it.
-你想要出路嗎  -你不想嗎
- You want out? - Don't you?
莉安
LeAnn...
我們做了違法的事
we have done some illegal things here.
還有其他競選
There are other campaigns.
-如果你可以打入國安局  -那不可能
- If you can get into the NSA... - That's not possible.
進入他們的系統  你可以解決的
...into their system, you can fix this.
-你沒聽我說  -我聽了
- You're not listening to me. - I am.
我了解安德伍德夫婦
I know the Underwoods.
我們如果想平安度過
The only way that we are gonna survive this...
就得讓他們贏
is if they win.
你可以幫他們贏
You can help them win.
我知道你能
I know you can.
你走后我就加入了報社
I got on the paper right around the time you left.
你從時尚版塊起步的嗎
Did you start in Style?
都市
Metro desk.
然后我發了篇報道  一個街頭時尚
But then I did this piece, a street fashion,
街頭的孩子的報道
kids on the street thing.
沒想到你會叫我來
I'm surprised you asked for me.
隊伍里有些人員變化
Some people are being moved around and off the team.
馬斯特森的報道  "戰爭  有什么好處"
The Masterson story. "War, what is it good for?"
你對調查性新聞感興趣嗎
Were you ever interested in investigative journalism?
要問我  不是這種的就不叫新聞
If you ask me, if it's not investigating, it's not journalism.
聽這里的人說  你能讓任何人對你開口
Word around here is you can get anybody to talk to you.
過了8點  又有酒的話
After 8:00, with a drink in their hands...
是啊
yeah.
他們說她是個...
She's the one they say you called a...
你懂的
you know.
對不起  我有點緊張
I'm sorry. I'm a little nervous.
你算是傳奇人物
You're sort of a legend and...
報道總統的文章
articles on the president?
能跟你合作是莫大的榮幸
It'd be an honor to work with you in any capacity.
能參與進來
To be part of this.
你們找到他了嗎
Did you find him? Did you?
再等一下就好
It'll only be another moment.
因為我已經做盡了一切
Because I've done all I can.
你們叫我做的一切  你知道的
Everything you told me to. You know that.
他們知道的  是吧
They know that, don't they?
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood.
我想跟馬斯特森女士說話
I was hoping to speak to Ms. Masterson.
就我們倆
Just the two of us.
有什么問題嗎
Is there a problem?
這有點極端
It is a bit extreme.
把禁飛令擴大到這樣的范圍
Expanding the no-fly list to this extent.
單是對簽證的限制就前所未有
The restrictions on visas alone is unprecedented.
我們要如何解釋
How do we justify?
白宮顧問已經討論過了
The White House counsel's been all through that.
都白紙黑字寫著了
It's there in black and white.
我們基本上是在
We're virtually closing down our borders
-沒有證據的情況下關閉國境  -會有的
- without any hard evidence to back it up. - It's coming.
很多無辜的人正想進入這個國家
A lot of innocent people are trying to get into this country.
他們可能因此受傷害
They could be hurt by this.
如此大的政策變動  我想好好做
A change in policy this big, I want it done right.
我要你讓世界知道
I want you to let the world know
如果他們還想繼續進入這個國家
that if they want to continue coming to this country
上我們的醫院  我們的學校
for our hospitals, our colleges,
我們的高爾夫球場什么的
our golf courses and God knows what else...
他們光是
they're going to have to deliver
把我的腦袋貼在棍子上燒是不夠的
more than my head on the end of a burning stick.
聽著  凱茜
Now look, Cathy,
我知道你有辛苦經營的人脈
I know you have well-earned relationships out there.
都是老交情
Long-standing.
我沒有保留  弗蘭西斯  我都聯絡了
I'm not holding back, Francis. I have reached out.
那我需要你再加把勁
Then I need you to reach further.
我要可行的情報
I want actionable intelligence.
我要知道哈里發國在哪  或者至少
I want to know where ICO is, or at the very least,
所有人都在找他們
that everyone's out there looking.
明白了嗎
Are we clear?
明白了
We're clear.
謝謝  凱茜  我知道你不會讓我失望
Thank you, Cathy. I know you won't let me down.
他死了
He's dead.
你是來告訴我這個的嗎
Is that why you're here?
我們還在找他
We're still looking for him--
因為如果他死了  我要見到他  摸到他
Because if he's dead, I want to see him. To touch him.
-我是想幫忙  -馬斯特森太太
- I'm trying to help... - Ms. Masterson,
-但他沒有聯系我  -求你
- ...but he hasn't contacted me. - please.
我也希望他聯系我
I wish he would.
我明白  冷靜
I understand. Calm down.
他不像他們說的那樣  是個禽獸
He's not a monster like they all say.
我不知何時失去了他  但他不是...
I lost him somewhere. But he's not...
但這世上還是有禽獸的  是吧
But still, monsters do exist, don't they?
我想要律師
I want my lawyer.
為什么
What for?
對不起  我不知道我為什么那么說
I'm sorry, I don't know why I said that.
我已經不知道我都在說什么了
I don't know why I say anything anymore.
我想見你
I wanted to see you...
是想問你一個簡單的問題
to ask you a simple question.
你不知道你家里發生的事嗎
Didn't you know what was going on in your home?
-什么  -你知道的
- Excuse me? - You knew...
早在他去巴基斯坦之前
even before he went to Pakistan.
-是你養大了他  -不
- I mean, you raised him. - No.
不  他是有問題  他迷失了
No. He had some problems. He got lost.
但不  不是這樣的
But no, nothing like this.
但你看到他做了什么吧
But you saw what he did, didn't you?
-不  -你想看嗎
- No. - Would you like to see it?
如果你想  我們可以給你看
We can show it to you, if you like.
不  別
No. Please don't.
他對那家人  對那個人做的事
What he did to that family, to that man...
什么樣的人能做出這種事
What sort of person would do such a thing?
他是我兒子
He's my son.
天吶
Oh, God.
我知道  很可怕  是吧
I know. It's awful, isn't it?
謝謝
Thank you.
你今天離開時
When you leave today,
會有記者  有攝像機在外面等著
there will be some reporters, some cameramen out there.
但你不需要說太多
But you don't need to say very much.
你只需要叫約書自首
You just need to ask Josh to turn himself in.
這世上還有很多辛辛苦苦的父親和母親
There are so many hardworking mothers and fathers out there.
這可能發生在他們任何人身上
This could've happened to any of them.
我們就要抓到你兒子了  馬斯特森太太
We are close to capturing your son, Ms. Masterson,
我會盡全力讓你見到他
and I will do my best to have you see him.
我想走了
I want to go.
沒人不讓你走
No one's keeping you.
但她安排了誰
But who did she put in?
議長安排了誰進委員會
Who did the Speaker put on the committee?
大多是席位無憂的長期議員
Mostly lifers, with secure seats.
還剩兩周  很難反對戰爭
We're two weeks out. It's hard to say no to war.
你和我有共同點
You and I have some things in common.
-我們都討厭總統  -不  我終歸是民主黨人
- We both dislike the president. - No. I'm still a Democrat.
但是右傾
Who leans to the right.
艾力克斯  你的確是有些右傾的
Alex, you do actually lean a little to the right.
他是三軍統帥
Look, he's the commander in chief.
他完全有權力決定去哪打仗
He's got all the authority he needs to fight them where they are.
此時此刻  國內就有個戰場
Well, there's one here. Out there, right now, as we speak.
我是很支持美國執法機構的
Well, I'm a big fan of American law enforcement.
他們很快就能找到他
They'll find him soon enough.
我們不能讓弗蘭西斯·安德伍德讓我們國家
We can't just let Francis Underwood turn us into a nation
變得時刻心驚膽戰
that's always looking over their shoulder.
如果你能擠進那個委員會
If you can get yourself onto that committee,
我覺得主席會讓你充分表達意見的
I got a feeling the Chair will give you all the time you need.
我的司機會送你回車上  但議員先生
My driver will take you back to your car. But, Congressman...
這是你的機會
this is your chance.
我覺得你也知道
And I think you know it.
非常感謝你們來
Thank you so much for coming out here.
Thank you so much for coming out.
見到你們真好  謝謝你們來
Great to see you. Thanks for coming out.
走開
Just go away!
你根本不知道自己家里發生的事
You have no idea what is happening in your own homes.
你知道他在哪嗎  馬斯特森太太
Have you any idea where he is, Mrs. Masterson?
約書  求你
Josh, please...
求你  求你自首吧
please, please turn yourself in.
這得停下了  不
This has all got to stop. No, no.
國家安全局
在財政部干了10年  他正等著呢
...this after ten years with Treasury, he was waiting for it.
是啊
Yeah...
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood!
政府是否認為爆炸跟
Does the administration believe that the explosion was connected
-約書亞·馬斯特森有關  -我們尚不確定
- with Joshua Masterson somehow? - We're not sure yet.
有很多證據支持這一可能性
Uh, there is strong evidence to suggest.
店主的確是在外國出生
The owner of the establishment was foreign-born.
跟海外的哈里發國有關嗎
Any connection to ICO overseas?
我認為助理局長
I think our Deputy Director
克拉克更有資格回答這個問題
Clark here is better equipped to answer that.
我們在調查  但現在  我們設立了熱線
We're looking into it. In the meantime, we've set up a hotline.
如果有任何居民
If anyone in the community
-有什么...  -如果共和黨候選人
- has any-- - And if the Republican candidate
和余下的共和黨人不肯承認
and the rest of his party refuse to acknowledge
國內威脅的嚴重性
the seriousness of the threat made here at home...
那么我們會的
know that we will.
聯調局正在收集言論和照片
The FBI is currently gathering a list of words and images.
如果它們出現在了你的孩子
If they appear on your children's
或你同事的設備上  請務必
or your coworkers' devices, please--
戰爭婊子
War whore!
-讓開  -上車
- Move! - Car!
就是油漆而已  她沒事
It was just paint. She's all right.
還有什么  說吧  道格  不會那么糟的
And what else? Spit it out, Doug. It won't taste so bad.
先生  我知道你在這事上跟我看法不同
Sir, I know you disagree with me on this.
但格林局長和他的團隊
But Director Green and his team
有了抓捕地點  準備行動了
have a location for the takedown and they're ready to act.
他們確定找對地方了嗎
And they're positive it's the right location?
-非常確定  -什么時候
- Adamant. - When?
再過幾小時
Hours.
我們可以在戰況室協調
We can coordinate out of the Situation Room.
不  我要親自見他
Oh, no. I'm gonna meet him in person.
先生  我強烈反對
Sir, I strongly advise against that.
知道了  但我要到場
Duly noted, but I'll be on-site.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
梅莉莎·米勒:"
你殺了我父親"
總統請求國會宣戰
人們隨時會爆發恐懼  真是不可思議
It's amazing how ready people are to be afraid.
歷史會證明他們是對的
History would prove them right.
幸好這個水能洗掉
You're lucky this is coming off with water.
可能會更糟呢
Could've been worse.
有點濺到你耳朵后面了
Some found its way behind your ear.
-我該害怕嗎  -別耍聰明
- Should I be afraid? - Don't be smart.
我是該害怕  是吧
I should, shouldn't I?
我從你那兒偷了東西
I stole something from you.
什么
What?
是什么無所謂
What it is, doesn't matter.
我就是想要一樣你的東西
I just wanted something that was yours.
放回去
Well, put it back.
瀑布
Waterfalls.
國安局用瀑布標記0day漏洞利用工具
The NSA marked their zero-day exploits as waterfalls.
它們能讓我們進入什么
What can they get us into?
我們可以后門進入一些很火的社交網站
We can backdoor into some very popular social media.
我可以把任何你能想到的東西
I can insert anything your imagination can think of
放到那些網站上
into those sites.
安德伍德夫婦或其他人的
Underwoods or otherwise.
多個消息源稱
...reports coming in from a variety of sources
當地警方和聯調局
stating that local police enforcement and FBI agents
正在前方
are currently on the ground.
我們接到報告稱
We're receiving reports that
弗吉尼亞州邊境有大量警力
there's a great deal of police activity on the Virginia border.
弗吉尼亞州邊境大規模警方行動
馬斯特森疑似在該區域
我們目前不能確認
We cannot confirm at this time,
但我們認為  這跟對國內恐怖分子
but we believe this is connected to the manhunt
約書亞·馬斯特森的搜尋有關
for domestic terrorist Joshua Masterson.
約書亞·馬斯特森可能很快將被捕
The capture of Joshua Masterson may be close at hand.
聯調局仍未就此發表評論
The FBI is still not commenting,
但請看航拍情況
but if you look at this aerial view,
可以看到全副武裝的人
you can see heavily-armed men
正在林間穿行
making their way through this wooded area.
長官  他不在這兒
Sir, he's not here.
我們只審出了一些零散的國內聯絡人
All we have are some loose domestic connections.
對海外哈里發國的變態崇拜
A perverse idolization of ICO overseas.
他不肯證實有大規模的國內網絡存在
He refuses to confirm any wide-ranging homegrown network.
我們的審訊官認為此人已無價值
Our interrogators are confident the asset is no longer valuable.
冒險誘供已經不可行了
And risk to reward no longer tenable.
先生  我們已經到達了臨界點
Sir, we have reached a breaking point.
你以為我沒有已經抓到了他
Did you think I didn't already have him?
我會任他在外面流竄嗎
That I would have left him out there somewhere?
我以為你了解我呢
And I thought you knew me.
約書
Josh.
約書亞
Joshua.
你想活嗎
Do you want to live?
說出我們想知道的
Tell us what we want.
Tell us what we want to hear.
你不是個殉道者  是吧
You're no martyr, are you?
看看你
Look at you.
不  你不是個殉道者
No, you're not a martyr.
沒人會記住你所做的事
No one will remember what you've done,
不管是在這人間  還是在你的天堂
either here on Earth or in your heaven.
你為什么選擇米勒一家
So why did you pick the Millers?
為什么
Why?
你看到了什么
What did you see?
是因為那女孩嗎
Was it the girl?
你是先看上了她嗎
Did you see her first?
你看上了什么
What did you see?
還是她先看到了你
Or did she see you first?
沒錯  就是這樣吧  她看到了你
Yeah, that's it, isn't it? She saw you.
她一眼就看穿了你  是吧
She looked right through you, didn't she?
我不需要再看到他了
I don't need to see this person anymore.
-處理掉他  -先生
- Get rid of the asset. - Sir.
他是個禽獸  但他終歸是美國公民
He's an animal, but he's still an American citizen.
我們在交戰  他是敵方戰斗人員
We are at war. And he is an enemy combatant.
他砍下那可憐人的腦袋時  就失去了一切
And he lost whatever rights he might have had as an American
美國人的權利
when he cut that poor man's head off.
所以少跟我說你的驕傲或立場
So don't give me your pride or your position.
因為如果你當初能照做
Because none of this would have happened
這一切都不會發生了
if you'd done what you were told in the first place.
我會處理的
I'll take care of it.
你當然會  而且會自愿自覺地做
Yes, you will, and you will do so willingly.
我要你拍到殺他時好的
And I want you to get some good, usable footage...
可用的錄像
of his killing.
然后銷毀其他一切
And then destroy everything else.
我們要發布約書亞·馬斯特森被殺的視頻
We will be releasing footage of Joshua Masterson's killing.
政府和情報機構
The administration and the intelligence community
本希望活捉他
were hoping to take him alive.
但我想贊揚
But I would like to commend
反恐處助理局長  納森·格林
Assistant Director of Counterterrorism, Nathan Green.
當然還有
And of course all of the work
國務卿杜蘭特做的一切相關幕后工作
that Secretary Durant has done behind the scenes on all of this.
調查目前為止收集到的信息
The information the investigation has gathered so far
表明約書亞·馬斯特森和扎克瑞·霍桑
points to Joshua Masterson and Zachary Hawthorne
跟海外的哈里發國
having strong connections to ICO abroad
和國內在發展的哈里發國網絡有密切關系
and ICO's growing network domestically.
所以我想直接對哈里發國說以下這些話
And so I would like to say this to ICO directly.
你們再別想左右哪怕一個年輕人的頭腦
You will not infect the mind of one more of our young people,
因為我不會罷休  直到我找到你
because I will not stop until I find you.
這話也說給悲痛中的米勒一家
And I say that for the grieving Miller family,
希望他們今晚能睡得著
whom I hope will find some sleep tonight.
我還敦促國會
I also urge Congress
加快進程
to accelerate the process
就我的宣戰請求做出表決
and vote on my request for a declaration of war.
-總統先生  -我不會回答問題
- Mr. President? - I will not be answering questions.
接下來賽斯會接手
Seth will take it from here.
不好分辨  但那應該是致命一擊
It's hard to see, but I think that was the killshot.
請記住  這些報道尚未經證實
Now, please remember, these reports are unconfirmed
我們還在等待白宮的聲明
and we're waiting on a statement from the White House.
我們可以報道  有大量...
What we can report is a great deal...
你為什么看這個
Why are you watching this?
...這片林區  有槍擊聲  既有...
...this wooded area. And shots being fired, both by and--
喂
Hello?
喂  我是弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
Hello. This is Francis Underwood.
是他
It's him.
委員會在找雷米·丹頓和杰姬·夏普
The committee is looking for Remy Danton and Jackie Sharp.
他們跟哈里發國和戰爭有什么關系
What do either of them have to do with ICO or the war?
國會那邊的消息是他們會要你
The talk up on the Hill is they're going to invite you
和你的手下去作證
and the rest of your staff to testify.
他們要利用宣戰的事做調查
They're gonna use the Declaration of War to investigate.
是的
That's right.
他們要用弗蘭克要求組建的委員會調查他
They're gonna use the committee Frank asked for to investigate him.
-該死  -是啊  道格
- Fuck. - That's right, Doug.
"該死"
"Fuck."
很難理解...
It's difficult to underst--
或許如果你能稍稍平靜一點
Well, perhaps if you could just calm down for a moment.
夠了
Please stop it.
我以為這消息能給你帶來一絲寬慰
I thought this news would bring you some relief.
總統打給了米勒太太
The president called Mrs. Miller.
我向你和你女兒保證過  我會...
I promised you and your daughter that I would--
放過她吧
Leave her alone.
或許我們還是
Well, perhaps we should speak
等你好一些了再談吧
when you're feeling a little more up to it.
我不想聽到你說話  或收到你的任何消息
I don't want to hear you. Or from you.
-你對我們家做的事...  -什么
- What you did to my family... - What?
別把我們扯進去  別用我丈夫的名字
Leave us out of it. And do not use my husband's name.
聽我說  太太
Listen, Mrs.--
她掛了
She hung up.
我們去走走吧
Let's go for a walk.
我們都是
吉姆·米勒
要犧牲多少
結束恐懼
為我們的自由而戰
總統先生
Mr. President!
說出他們想聽的
Tell them what they need to know.
總統先生
Mr. President!
你們好
Hello.
總統先生  謝謝  謝謝
Mr. President. Thank you, thank you.
你好
Hello.
你們完全不需要害怕
You have nothing to be afraid of.
你完全不需要害怕
■
"宣戰權"在美國法律和政府實踐中是一個比較混亂的灰色區域
美國憲法規定國會擁有正式宣戰權  但又規定美國總統是三軍統帥
作為行政機構的首腦  歷史上  美國總統經常援引后一條規定
以自己作為三軍統帥有絕對的軍事指揮權為由繞過國會  發動軍事行動
事實上  二戰之后  美國總統發動大規模軍事行動時  從未尋求國會授權
為了奪回宣戰權  國會1973年通過了《戰爭權力法案》
但該法案同時規定  總統可以先發動軍事行動  后在90天內尋求國會授權
73年的法案通過后  除了大小布什發動兩次海灣戰爭時獲得了國會授權
其余絕大多數情況下  美國總統都無視這個法律的存在
所以現實中  "國會授權"反而成了總統想回避軍事行動時的一個借口
而真正下決心采取行動時  反而可以不用理會國會